They were always here
Project Ithaca is a science fiction, thriller film
directed by Nicholas Humphries.
Five strangers awaken to find themselves trapped aboard an alien spaceship
that seems to be harnessing their terror to power the ship.
They begin to understand that these species have been
abducting humans for decades and possibly centuries.
Sera, played by Deragh Campbell.
John Brighton, played by James Gallanders.
Perry Bulmer, played by Daniel Fathers.
Alex Gauthier, played by Caroline Raynaud.
Zack Chase, played by Alex Woods.
Project Ithaca is a 2019 Canadian science fiction thriller film
directed by Nicholas Humphries and starring James Gallanders.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.